I wonder if you're reluctant to call them dictators in Cuba and Venezuela.
I'm not reluctant. I just haven't thought about them that often. I'll be honest with you.
I think that Maduro's government is one of repression. There's no question about it.
It's always in Cuba.
Sorry?
And also it's happened in Cuba since 1959.
And I think that the repression that, whether we're speaking about Cuban New Yorkers or Venezuelan New Yorkers,
that they have had to live through, is a repression that stands in a clear contrast from what our vision is.
This guy is not that girl.
So if you watched Views for Amanda Lane yesterday on YouTube and Amanda Seals TV,
you saw a really dope debate that sprung up between me and my guest, Dr. Shola Mas-Mogbamimu,
about voting and the efficacy of voting.
And one of her points was that in seeing someone like Zohan Mamdani actually get the mayorship
with all of the hindrances put upon him,
it should be encouraging that we, as the people, actually have the power to control
who gets put into these positions, which I want to believe.
But when you see Mamdani show up like this,
it dawned on us that, I guess I should provide some context for those who don't know,
when I say he's showing up like this, I mean,
at a time when they are actively trying to start a war in Venezuela to steal resources,
a real socialist would never say anything that sounds like this capitalist imperialist government.
Still, it helps to support the point that I was making in our interview,
which became somewhat of a debate, well, it became a debate,
but like a truly intellectual debate, which I really appreciate that we were able to have.
And that is that there are people who are put in positions
to create a particular response for the people.
And I'm genuinely beginning to wonder if the Democrat pushback that Mamdani was getting
was genuine.
Like, I'm genuinely beginning to wonder if that was actually just controlled opposition
to make people feel like they got a win.
So that when he came in and started doing their bidding,
we would be quiet about it.
What thoughts does this clip evoke for you?
Drop them in the comments.